goodfirms.co 2019-07-06

# Privacy Policy of GoodFirms

At GoodFirms your privacy is important. It is committed to respecting your privacy and protecting your personally-identifiable information. Here GoodFirms describes how it uses the information it collects for its research purposes. The information is collected through the website ([www.goodfirms.co](https://www.goodfirms.co/)), surveys - both online and offline and from third party. It is important that you read this Privacy Policy carefully. The word ‘you’ or ‘users’ is used to denote visitors who visit the site or use any of its services. When you visit GoodFirms’ website or submit information to it whether online or offline, you consent to the use, collection and disclosure of the information it has about you in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

#### What is GoodFirms?

GoodFirms aims at finding the best companies in the App development landscape. It provides quality research support for both buyers and sellers of service providers in the industry. GoodFirms provides categorized directory, authoritative research, evaluated content and resources based on its numerous online and offline initiatives. It helps the clients in being more effective by making informed decision and seizing opportunities.

App developers are looking for good clients and companies who need apps; service seekers who need their apps developed are searching for app developers that are a cut above the rest. Aided by evaluations, client reviews and other specific methodologies GoodFirms brings them together on the portal through the user accounts by sharing required information as and when required. 

#### Information GoodFirms collects

The information GoodFirms collects about the companies and their services is through enquiry and research methodologies. GoodFirms zeroes in on relevant companies and lists them after appropriation. Other companies which are interested in participating in the research provide necessary information, testimonials and reviews about other companies too. Companies who use GoodFirms’ services create user accounts and user profiles. GoodFirms will ask you for your credit card details if you purchase any of its services. 

GoodFirms may collect your information through several different online and offline channels. It can be via website, through Registration forms, user log-ins, emails, in person, over the phone, through internal and third-party web based survey tools. The personal information it collects in general includes but is not limited to name, mailing address, email address, telephone numbers, gender, date of birth, occupation, education and other similar demographic information. 

GoodFirms uses website analytics services like Google Analytics to collect data. These services use cookies. Most browsers accept cookies automatically by default. When a visitor visits GoodFirms, he consents to the placement of cookies in his browser in agreement with GoodFirms’ Privacy Policy. 

When you visit GoodFirms’ website, it automatically collects information about the timing of your visit, IP address, the pages you visit, the links you click on, Operating System, the browser you use, the device you use to view our website and the screen resolution of that device. 

####  Use of information 

GoodFirms’ website, records the details of your visit and logs your information for administrative and research purposes. The IP addresses and other information helps it create user profiles. User profiles help in predicting user behaviour which in turn helps GoodFirms make the site userfriendly. Information related to day, date and time of users’ visits helps GoodFirms in scheduling its maintenance tasks and enables it to utilize its prime time well. GoodFirms tracks the navigation, pages you visit, duration of your visit and the downloads you are interested in to know you better. Personally-identifiable information is stored and is used to contact you, to keep you informed and obtain your views of GoodFirms’s services and activities. It is also for statutory and regulatory compliance and for processing any enquiries raised by you with respect to your dealings with GoodFirms.

Testimonials and reviews received about app developing companies and app developers listed with us may be posted by GoodFirms on the website. Testimonials may carry the name of the provider along with its company’s name and any other suitable information that is provided to us. 

Cookies are for identifying you and your interests. They are used to track the way you use the site. GoodFirms uses cookies for engagement and to process any requests you make. 

#### Disclosure of information

GoodFirms takes and shall take reasonable steps to prevent unauthorized or accidental disclosure of your personally-identifiable information. GoodFirms shall not intentionally transfer or disclose any of your personally-identifiable information to third parties without your consent except as follows. 

GoodFirms may provide access to your personally-identifiable information to third party vendors engaged by it only when such vendor first agrees on maintaining the strict confidentiality of such information and agrees to provide the same level of data security as provided by GoodFirms. GoodFirms may surrender personal information to affected parties and legal authorities if presented with a court order as required and permitted by the laws, rules and regulations of any applicable jurisdiction in furtherance of potential or on-going legal proceedings. 

#### Opt-Out / Unsubscribe / Change, and / or Delete information 

Your right to deactivate or delete your account from GoodFirms is subject to our records retention policies and applicable law, including any statutory retention requirements. You are well within your rights to access, correct, update and/or delete any information you submit to the site. However, please note that the company profile cannot be deleted once it includes even a single review. This is not possible as we cannot delete information that is shared by a third-party. If you are not interested in the updates, Direct mailers and newsletters from GoodFirms, you can unsubscribe from mailing lists, registrations from the site. You can also contact GoodFirms and ask to unsubscribe.

GoodFirms uses cookies where they are necessary for its services or where it has user’s implied or express consent. People who visit the site can inspect, block or delete cookies with right settings in browsers and with right tools. 

If you are in any way concerned about providing information on GoodFirms website in any manner permitted in GoodFirms’ Privacy Policy, you should refrain from using the website. Write to us in case you are concerned about any review or testimonial. 

#### Data Security

GoodFirms takes and implements generally accepted standards of technology and operational security to protect your personal information from unauthorised access, use, disclosure or loss while in transmission or storage. It has both online and offline safeguards in place to prevent misuse, destruction and alteration of information. Only authorized GoodFirms’ employees and vendors are provided access to personally-identifiable information. Systems are routinely monitored for potential vulnerabilities and attacks. At your end you are advised to keep your login information secure. 

#### Data Retention

Strategically gathered industry related data remains with us as long as we are not specifically asked to remove it. If you have a user account, related information is with us for as long as your account is active or is needed for legal, regulatory or administrative purposes. We may keep your information with us even after you close your account to resolve disputes, prevent frauds and abuse or as a part of our data backup process. 

#### Video Review Guidelines

The video reviewer can avail the benefit of an incentive ($20 Amazon Gift Card) for at most 5 reviews.

#### Notification of changes

By using (visiting) the GoodFirms’ site, you consent to the collection, use and storage of your information by GoodFirms in the manner described in this Privacy Policy and elsewhere on the site. GoodFirms reserves the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of the Privacy Policy at any time, at its discretion. Your continued use of the site following the changes in Privacy Policy will mean that you accept the changes. 

If you have any questions about GoodFirms Privacy Policy or if you require any assistance in navigating the site and reading the provided material, you can contact us at: **info@goodfirms.co**
